mayajaal.com 2006-12-18

# Mayajaal

This site is used for information purpose(s) only. The information, Software, Products and Services included in our website may include inaccuracies or typographical errors. Changes are periodically made to our website in this regard. Accordingly, we do not guarantee the accuracy, timeliness, reliability or completeness of any of the information contained on, downloaded or accessed from this website.

Your use of this website or of any content presented in any and all areas of the website indicates your acknowledgment and agreement to these Terms of Use, our Privacy Policy and other notices posted on this website. If you do not agree to be bound by and comply with all of the foregoing, you may not access or use our information, services, or website. We suggest you print a copy of each of these documents for your records.

**Information Use and Disclosure**

Mayajaal does not disclose information about your individual visits to Mayajaal’s Website or Personal information that you provide to us to any outside parties without your prior permission. Before submitting personal information using the Mayajaal website, you will be required to give Mayajaal permission to use your personal information as necessary to perform the requested service(s) and to affirm your understanding and agreement with this privacy policy. If you choose not to permit use of your personal information or to affirm your understanding and agreement with this privacy policy, you will be unable to use the services that require your personal information and you will only be able to access generalized portions of the website.

In general, the personal information that you submit to Mayajaal is only shared within the company on a “need to know” basis, in order to fulfill your requests.

Mayajaal will also share your personal information with authorized third parties when we believe it is required by law or to protect Mayajaal, our website users, or others.

  **Third Party Websites  
**  
Links or pointers to other websites and references to products and services offered by third parties are provided to you for convenience only and do not constitute an endorsement or approval by us of (i) the organizations that operate such websites; (ii) the content, privacy policies or other terms of use on such websites; or (iii) such third party products and services. As we have no control or responsibility over websites or content maintained by other organizations, or for products and services offered by third parties, we do not assume any liability for your use of any of the foregoing, which use you acknowledge and agree shall be at your own risk.
